Guide to the George P. Hall & Son Photograph Collection [1876-1914] PR 24
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series VI: Logbooks
  Series consists of two logbooks reflecting the work of George P. Hall & Son. While they provide a valuable record of the firm's work from 1895 on, they are of very limited use as a guide to this collection. The indexes are arranged roughly alphabetically and thereunder by size, but subjects are sometimes entered by surnames; surnames sometimes refer to the company or individual for whom work was done, but may sometimes refer to the photographer. Many photographs are indexed only under very general subjects. Because in many cases images in this collection no longer bore the original photographer's number or description at the time of processing, the indexes are not a particularly useful tool for accessing this collection.
  - Logbook 1, [1895-1914] (Volume 1)
  - Logbook 2, [1895-1914] (Volume 2)